{
    "games": [
        {
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "arobase",
                    "content": [
                        " sign in ",
                        " password",
                        " slash",
                        " at"
                    ],
                    "correct": 3
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "banni\u00e8re",
                    "content": [
                        " networking",
                        " down",
                        " post ",
                        " banner "
                    ],
                    "correct": 3
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "discuter",
                    "content": [
                        " sign in ",
                        " underscore",
                        " comment ",
                        " chat "
                    ],
                    "correct": 3
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "commentaire",
                    "content": [
                        " hyphen",
                        " post ",
                        " comment ",
                        " font "
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "en panne",
                    "content": [
                        " username",
                        " down",
                        " load",
                        " comment "
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "entrer",
                    "content": [
                        " enter ",
                        " banner ",
                        " down",
                        " post "
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "suivre",
                    "content": [
                        " down",
                        " underscore",
                        " follow",
                        " chat "
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "police de caract\u00e8res",
                    "content": [
                        " font ",
                        " sign in ",
                        " comment ",
                        " enter "
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "trait d'union",
                    "content": [
                        " enter ",
                        " hyphen",
                        " online",
                        " networking"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "lien",
                    "content": [
                        " hyphen",
                        " online",
                        " networking",
                        " link "
                    ],
                    "correct": 3
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "charger",
                    "content": [
                        " underscore",
                        " font ",
                        " load",
                        " username"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "r\u00e9seautage",
                    "content": [
                        " networking",
                        " underscore",
                        " load",
                        " sign in "
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "en ligne",
                    "content": [
                        " slash",
                        " post ",
                        " update",
                        " online"
                    ],
                    "correct": 3
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "mot de passe",
                    "content": [
                        " hyphen",
                        " underscore",
                        " password",
                        " sign in "
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "message",
                    "content": [
                        " follow",
                        " online",
                        " underscore",
                        " post "
                    ],
                    "correct": 3
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "se connecter",
                    "content": [
                        " sign in ",
                        " username",
                        " slash",
                        " hyphen"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "barre oblique",
                    "content": [
                        " link ",
                        " slash",
                        " password",
                        " username"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "tiret du bas",
                    "content": [
                        " enter ",
                        " underscore",
                        " follow",
                        " sign in "
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "mise \u00e0 jour",
                    "content": [
                        " link ",
                        " update",
                        " password",
                        " down"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "identifiant",
                    "content": [
                        " password",
                        " font ",
                        " load",
                        " username"
                    ],
                    "correct": 3
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}